This is because I didn't take
the time to listen to her.
Could she have... run away from home?
Van?
"Must get medicine... from the Vankreift
family... we must... the young lady."
I heard a voice saying that.
What did you say?!
Could it be...
Was she mistakenly kidnapped instead of me?
Uncle, I-I'm sorry...
Ellen, it's not your fault.
Please don't cry.
But... But because of
the medicine I made, she...
Your work has saved a great many lives.
The people who kidnapped
Rafilia are the ones to blame.
Not you, Ellen.
Your Grace.
What is it?
Before milady's disappearance, she received
a letter from His Highness Gadiel.
Why would he send her a letter?
Prince Gadiel previously came
to visit Lady Ellen.
Yes, I was informed of that.
Ever since Rafilia and the prince met,
they've been exchanging letters.
Pardon me, but this is the letter.
It was left on her desk,
so I assume she read it today.
Prince Gadiel has summoned Rafilia.
So the one who kidnapped her—
Wait! Are you saying the group after
Ellen's medicine is the royal family?
If His Highness has summoned her,
that seems likely.
Still...
She also could have been grabbed
going to see His Highness.
There is that possibility, yes.
We don't know why the prince
even summoned her.
Van.
Could you hear them saying "the prince,"
"young lady," and "medicine"?
Yeah. Sounds like they're snooping around.
They're here?! In our domain?
Yes, they are.
Then perhaps it was His Highness...
Where? Where are they?!
Take me to them right now!
THE KIDNAPPING INCIDENT
Perhaps the spirits are involved after all.
It seems no one knows the identity
of the Healing Princess.
Indeed.
If only we could uncover
the nature of her medicines.
However, there are terms you must
adhere to in your research, Hume.
The Vankreifts are very special
to the royal family, after all.
The conditions His Majesty
set forth were to include the prince
on this journey and my research
on the medicines... But why?
Gaddis.
What is it?
Have you ever met the hero's daughter?
What?
Highness, please stand back!
I can protect myself!
Give back my daughter.
You're... What are you doing here?
Silence. You lured out my daughter
to have her kidnapped, didn't you?!
Ashute?
Where is my daughter?!
Watch your mouth!
Get out of my way!
Wait, Uncle!
Ellen...
They're saying Rafilia isn't here.
What?
I confirmed it with the spirits,
so please calm down, Uncle.
Just as I thought.
She's not? Rafilia's... not here?
Ellen!
I've wanted to see you.
No... Don't come near me!
What?!
I ask that you not approach my daughter.
Rovel Vankreift!
Did you forget what happened three years ago?
I haven't forgotten.
That's why I want to apologize.
Three years ago?
That's right!
That was when the royal family
discovered they're cursed by the spirits.
Now then, let's hear it, shall we?
Prince Gadiel, why did you summon my daughter?
What do you mean?
After receiving this, my daughter snuck out
of the mansion and hasn't been seen since.
A letter?
Don't play dumb with me!
You're the one who called for her!
Cut the crap, Sauvel Vankreift!
Vogel!
Duke Sauvel, please let me see that.
It's true that Rafilia and I
have been exchanging letters.
However, I did not write this.
That's the royal crest! There's no
talking your way around that.
It is, yes.
Still, I swear I did not write this.
Please believe me.
Then what brings you here?
Research.
Rumors say the Vankreift family possesses
medicines effective against the epidemic.
Your Highness!
There's no point in hiding it.
The only way to prove that we didn't
kidnap Rafilia is to speak up.
You truly are the king's son.
I'm glad to see you're quick on the uptake.
We only meant to research the source
and the effects of the medicine.
In fact, the king has been worried.
Worried?
According to the rumors,
your skilled apothecary is Ellen.
So before something happens to her,
he ordered me to find out the truth.
Why would Mr. Blackheart be worried
about me? What is he scheming?
But he'd never kidnap Rafilia to that end!
Are you the spirit princess?
Huh? I'm...
And who might you be?
I am Hume, a court healer.
I see.
I have a spirit friend named Ashute.
It's very cute.
Even though he serves the royal family?
You have a pact with a spirit?
Yep, we're best friends. Don't believe me?
Then I'll show you.
But Your Highness, don't come
near us no matter what, okay?
Come on out, Ashute.
Let me introduce you. Look, Ashute.
Pwincess!
That's what I thought.
You really are the spirit princess.
I always had my suspicions that spirits were
somehow involved with the medicines.
Now it all makes sense.
I assume that makes you
the Healing Princess as well.
Father, I believe it's about time
that we tell them.
Ellen, are you serious?
Yes. Rumors of the medicines have
already reached the royal capital.
Nice to meet you. My name is Ellen.
As you said, I am the spirit queen's daughter.
The spirit queen's daughter?
Allow me to explain the effects
of the medicines you're after.
Are you certain, Ellen?
Yes. The king already knows of them.
It would be best for the
royal family to manage them
rather than have the
Vankreifts monopolize them.
Also, concerning His Majesty's worry for me...
That's because he fears my father and I
leaving this world if I'm compromised.
Things are just as the king wants.
What do you mean?
Our current predicament with Rafilia
works in His Majesty's favor.
Now, if it turns out the royal family
had anything to do with the kidnapping...
You had best be prepared.
I told you I don't know anything of it!
There's no way His Majesty
would have told you.
That's just the kind of man he is.
Have I been used by my own father?
If we find Rafilia, it will prove
your innocence beyond a doubt.
So please help us with the search.
You're asking the prince to help?
You have already failed your mission.
Do you want to report that to His Majesty?
What choice do we have?
I'm certain he'd meet such failure
with a disappointed sigh.
But what if you could redeem
your failure by finding Rafilia?
What do you mean?
I'm offering a deal.
If you help me, I'll give you the details,
as well as a sample,
of the medicines at once.
It's what His Majesty wants,
so if you take it to him,
your mission will be a success.
Do we have your word?
I am the spirit queen's daughter.
On my pride as the heir to the Primordial King...
I swear it.
The Primordial King...
However, only on the condition
that Rafilia is rescued safely.
Understood.
As her friend, I'm worried
about Rafilia as well.
Then we have a deal.
I bet you'd need a decent number
of men to kidnap a noble girl.
Ellen, why are you asking for their help?
Three at the very least,
and they wouldn't be going on foot.
Rafilia's life is at stake.
We can't afford to be stingy, Father.
That's certainly true.
The culprits likely used
a carriage to grab her,
then stashed it somewhere inconspicuous.
Yeah.
A path that a carriage could use...
Where does this road here lead?
A quarry that our ancestors
used to use, I believe.
No one goes there anymore, though...
That's it!
Let's gather intel using
the power of the wind.
Van, could you search
around this area from above?
I'm on it.
I'm counting on you.
A high-ranking spirit...
He's a great spirit. They're the only ones
who can take human form, after all.
Oh! You were using the power of the wind
to blow away the disease, weren't you?
You noticed that?
I thought there must be a
high-ranking wind spirit around, but...
I see. That's another way to use such power.
This Hume boy.... He has a
very high affinity with the spirits.
Sauvel.
Let us await the report first.
Uncle, I'm sure it'll be fine.
Yeah. I'm sorry.
Thank you, Ellen.
If only we knew what she looked like,
we could use the water mirror.
True enough.
More like, if only you remembered
what Rafilia looked like...
Sorry. I'm drawing a blank.
Well, Father, I suppose you do avoid women.
Van, please hurry.
Ellen.
Oh, sorry. Please don't run.
I have one favor to ask.
If we manage to find Rafilia safely,
I ask that you hear me out.
I wonder if the day will come that you
and the spirits ever forgive me.
I'll be back.
Okay. I will.
Huh?
Ellen.
The curse will activate, so you
mustn't go near His Highness.
I know that!
Hey, Ellen. Why were you
staring at the prince?
Oh, I found it strange that
he was smiling so happily
when I merely agreed that I'd speak with him.
I forgot. When it comes to yourself,
you're absolutely clueless, Ellen.
What is that supposed to mean?
Just that you're Miss Clueless! That's all!
Princess!
Van! How did it go?
As you thought, princess. There appear
to be seven men and one young girl.
Well done!
Let's go, Sauvel!
Right!
Wait a minute! What about us?
Wait at my mansion.
Kai, I leave the prince to you!
What? But I'm...
Kai.
Are you ready?! Let's go!
Please, be safe!
How long do we gotta stay like this?
We were told to wait for
further instructions, 'member?
Huh?
Th-The hell are you guys?!
Van, where is the girl?
In the cave up ahead.
Hey, what's going on?
One, two, three, four, five, six...
Hey! What's up?
One's missing. Where's the last one?
I can sense a man deep within the cave.
Sauvel, I'll take care of things here.
You go get your daughter.
Understood.
Don't ya be whispering!
If ya got no business, then—
Go, Sauvel!
I owe you one, Brother!
What?
As if we'd let you pass!
Hey!
I'm your opponent.
Who are these people?
They're probably some vigilante group
hired to rescue the brat.
You lot dared to meddle with something
you absolutely shouldn't have.
You'll pay for that in full.
Wait, Rovel!
Ori!
Mother?!
Wh-What the...?
Who's that?
Why are you here?
Because! My precious, precious
little Ellen is working so hard...
Of course I want to pitch in too.
I can, can't I?
Of course you can.
That's... Why is she here?
Hey, what's wrong?!
I-I saw her before during the Monster Tempest.
What are you talking about?
That...
That's... Spirit Queen Origin!
Then that means... that guy is
the hero who saved the world!
It's been ages since we've
fought together, hasn't it, Rovel?
Yeah.
Since the Monster Tempest, I'd say.
Brings back memories.
Let us do our best.
Smooch!
Now, let's show them what we got!
Our powers... together!
I've never seen this before.
So this is my parents' power?
Oh my! Did we get a little too carried away?
But I feel so much better now!
See you later, my sweet Ellen!
Rafilia...
Rafilia?
Rafilia!
Who the hell're you guys?
What do you want?
I came to take my daughter back.
Your daughter? Parents weren't invited here.
I'll leave Rafilia to you.
Right!
Hey, hey! Don't go thinkin'
you got the run of the place!
Father!
What's wrong? Can't do nothin', huh?!
Wha— Barehanded?!
I can't move it! Who the hell are...
I am the knight commander of the
Tenbahl Kingdom, Sauvel Vankreift!
What? The knight commander?!
Take this!
Wait—
Father!
Rafilia!
Are you hurt? Are you all right?!
Father!
I'm glad... I'm so glad.
I'm sorry for everything, Rafilia.
Father...
Let's go home.
Yeah.
Oh, Uncle!
How is Rafilia?
She's fine.
She was probably tense this whole time.
She fell asleep.
Alberto, please hand these guys
over to the guard.
Understood.
Brother, sorry for worrying you.
No need to thank me.
I'm glad your daughter is safe.
Yes.
Thank goodness.
Translation: Yukari Murase-Louden
Editing: Riley Dalton
Quality Check: Ashley Barboza
Translation Check: Elizabeth Ellis